{
    "subject": "resource/Christopher_Reid_(entertainer)",
    "predicate": "property/name",
    "object": "Christopher \"Kid\" Reid",
    "human_readable": "The name of Christopher Reid (entertainer) is Christopher 'Kid' Reid.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8848292827606201,
            "question": "Is Christopher 'Kid' Reid a musician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8428347706794739,
            "question": "Has Christopher 'Kid' Reid acted in films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8395997881889343,
            "question": "What genre of music is Christopher 'Kid' Reid known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8174388408660889,
            "question": "Who is the other member of the comedy duo with Christopher 'Kid' Reid?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8172292113304138,
            "question": "What famous comedy duo was Christopher 'Kid' Reid a part of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7987759709358215,
            "question": "Is Christopher 'Kid' Reid still active in the entertainment industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7649782299995422,
            "question": "What is Christopher Reid's stage name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5978972315788269,
            "question": "What were some of Christopher 'Kid' Reid's most popular songs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5760824680328369,
            "question": "When did Christopher 'Kid' Reid gain popularity?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5060815811157227,
            "question": "Has Christopher 'Kid' Reid won any awards for his work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Christopher Reid (entertainer) is Christopher 'Kid' Reid.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7907_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When did Christopher 'Kid' Reid gain popularity?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7907_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were some of Christopher 'Kid' Reid's most popular songs?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7907_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Christopher Reid's stage name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7907_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7907_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7907_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7907_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7907_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7907_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7907_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7907_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7907_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7907_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7907_54.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Christopher \"KID\" Reid, confirming that his name is indeed Christopher \"Kid\" Reid. This supports the statement that the name of the entertainer Christopher Reid (entertainer) is Christopher 'Kid' Reid."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}